Rockville Journal World War II Letters
Vernon Historical Society
- Inventory
  - Schneider, Norman R, undated; Chalons; France; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schneider, Norman R, undated; Chalons-sur-Marne; France; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schneider, William, undated; Hawaii; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schneider, Edward J, undated; Somers Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schneider, Ernest G, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 10 West Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schneider, William, undated; Asheville; NC; Military Record,Reassignment; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schneider, William, undated; Luzon; Philippines; Military Anecdote; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schnieder, Norman R, undated; Fort Devens,MA; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schnieder, Elmer W, undated; Seattle,WA; Scenery; Mount Rainier; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schortman, John B, undated; USS Steinaker; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schortman, John B, undated; Navy; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schrumpf, Raymond Jr, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Killled France, 21; Son of M&M R Schrumpf,Wife Lillian; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schrumpf, Raymond Jr., undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schub, Walter E, undated; Hondo,TX; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schub, Walter E, undated; Greensboro; NC; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schub, Walter E, undated; Springfield Ohio; Arrived for Flight Training; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schub, Walter E, undated; Lowry Field; Denver,CO; Graduated from Air Armament Course; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schub, Walter E, undated; European Theater; Completed Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schub, Walter E, undated; Randolph Field; TX; Discharged with Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schultz, William J, undated; APO San Francisco; CA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schumey, John E, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 38 Lawrence Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Scibek, Edward, undated; Norfolk,VA; Camp Life; Stadium,Naval Training Station; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Scibek, Edward, undated; New York City; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Scibek, Stefan K, undated; Zellam See; Austria; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Scibek, Stefan K, undated; North Africa; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Scibek, Edward, undated; Sampson,NY; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Scibek, Stefan K, undated; 12th AAF; Italy; Received Award,Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sedlacek, William F, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Killed Italy,27; Son of M&M Martin Sedlacek,RFD #2; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Seff, Alden, undated; Little Creek,VA; Camp Life; See Neff, Alden; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Seifert, Warren, undated; Norfolk Army Base; VA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Seifert, Warren, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Fort Sam Houston,TX; Son of Mrs Henry Seifert,RFD #2; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Seifert, Raymond A, undated; Birmingham; AL; Appointed Officer; Military (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Seifert, Raymond A, undated; Birmingham; AL; Appointed Officer; Military (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Seifert, Raymond A, undated; Birmingham; AL; Appointed Officer; Military (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Seligson, Arnold, undated; Camp Makall,NC; Camp Life; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Serafin, H, undated; Long Beach,CA; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Shapera, Harry A, undated; Robins Field,GA; Camp Life; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Shapera, Harry A, undated; Fort McClellan; AL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Shapera, Harry A, undated; Westover Field; MA; Discharged; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sharp, Herbert E, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sharp, Herbert E, undated; Napier Field; AL; Received Pilot's Wings; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sharp, Herbert E, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Shea, James E, undated; Fort Dix; NJ; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Shea, John D, undated; Shoemaker; CA; Discharged; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Shepard, Eva M, undated; Cleveland,OH; Camp Life; Stage Door Canteen, Cleveland,OH; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Shepard, Eva M, undated; Bronx,NY; Camp Life; Hunter College; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Shepard, Eva M, undated; Cleveland; OH; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Shepard, Eva M, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Shepard, Eva M, undated; US Naval Barracks; NY; Discharged as WAVE,Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sherburne, Carleton, undated; Jefferson Proving Ground; Madison, IN; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sherburne, Carleton, undated; Jefferson Proving Ground; Madison, IN; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sherburne, Carleton, undated; Glendale; CA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sherburne, Carleton, undated; Schick General Hospital; Clinton, IA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sherman, Robert, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Was POW; Released and Home,Aerial Gunner; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sherman, Robert S, undated; Commisioned as 2nd Lieutenant; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Shields, Peter, undated; 129th General Hospital; England; Recovering from Injury,Interview; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Shortman, R.A., undated; Nashville,TN; Humor; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Shortman, J, undated; FPO San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Shortman, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Shortmann, Richard C, undated; New Guinea; with Enclosure Newsletter; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Shortmann, Richard C, undated; Philippines; See Schortmann, Richard C; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Siedlik, Stanley T, undated; China; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Siedlik, Stanley T, undated; North Africa; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Siedlik, Stanley T, undated; APO NYC; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Siedlik, Stanley T, undated; China; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Siedlik, Stanley T, undated; China; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Siedlik, Stanley T, undated; China; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Siedlik, Stanley T, undated; New York City; NY; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Siedlik, Stanley T, undated; India; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Siedlik, Stanley T, undated; Kumming; China; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Siedlik, Stanley T, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Siedlik, Stanley T, undated; Mary Halenan; Service Update; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Siedlik, Frank J., undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Siegel, Saul, undated; Rapid City,SD; Scenery; Badlands,SD; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Siegel, Herman S, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Awarded Citation; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sierakowski, Francis J, undated; Poenixville; PA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sierakowski, Francis J, undated; Augusta; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sierakowski, Walter J, undated; APO NYC; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sierakowski, Walter J, undated; North Reading; MA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sierakowski, Walter J, undated; New York City; POW; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sierakowski, Francis J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 40 High Street; Son of Mr and Mrs John Sierakowski; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sierakowski, Walter J, undated; Italy; Description of 51st Military Police Company; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Silhevy, Ernest S, undated; 8th Air Force; England; On List of 8th AF after VE Day; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Silverware, Rabbi, undated; Rockville,CT; Humor; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Simpson, Everett A, undated; Tolland Honor Roll; Killed Okinawa,21; Son of Mr and Mrs Roland Simpson; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skinner, Leroy B, undated; Fort Bragg,NC; Camp Life; One Post Card, w George Beyers; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skinner, Donald W, undated; Italy; with Special Order of the Day; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skinner, Donald W, undated; Photo Sent by Mother; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skinner, Donald W, undated; North Africa; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skinner, George U, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skinner, George U, undated; Camp Forrest; TN; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skinner, George U, undated; New Address, Mrs Luther Skinner; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skinner, Priscilla, undated; Latrobe, PA; St Vincent College; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skinner, George U, undated; Landshut; Germany; with "Progress of Battery D"; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skinner, Donald W, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skinner, G Nelson, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skinner, Donald W, undated; Mother; Service Update; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skinner, Donald W, undated; 12th AAF; Awarded Badge, Battle Description; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skinner, Donald W, undated; Mediterranean Theater; Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skinner, Donald W, undated; 12th AAF; Promoted; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skinner, Donald W, undated; Sicily; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skipper, Catherine A, undated; Manila; Philippines; Waiting for Assignment to Hospital; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sklodosky, Chester M, undated; Camp Wheeler; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skoglund, Ernest L, undated; Lido Beach,NY; Humor; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skoglund, Ernest L, undated; Davisville,RI; Humor; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skoglund, Ernest L, undated; Camp Peary,VA; Seabees; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skoglund, Ernest L, undated; Davisville,RI; Seabees; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skoglund, Ernest L, undated; Lido Beach; Long Island NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skoglund, Ernest L, undated; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skoglund, Ernest L, undated; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skoglund, Ernest L, undated; Lido Beach; Long Island NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skoglund, Ernest L, undated; France; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skoglund, Ernest L, undated; Long Island; NY; with Enclosure; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skoglund, Ernest L, undated; Davisville; RI; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skoglund, Ernest L, undated; Davisville; RI; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skoglund, Ernest L, undated; Davisville; RI; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Skoglund, Leonard, undated; 8th Bomber Station; England; Earned Promotion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Slack, Steven, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Slivinsky, Joseph A, undated; Norfolk; VA; Arrived for Training on a Destroyer; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Slye, Richard H, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Received Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Slye, Richard H, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Received Commendation; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Smith, Shirley, undated; Middletown; CT; on Postcard Under Brown, Marion; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Smith, Edmund C, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Smith, William F, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Smith, Edmund C, undated; Mrs Edmund Smith; Promotion,Military Record; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Smith, Charles L Jr, undated; Philippines; Home on Furlough,Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Smith, Earl W, undated; Alaska; Serving as Paratrooper; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Smith, Emma, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Snadel, Edward F, undated; Austria; Enlisted in Army; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Snydal, Stanley J, undated; South Pacific; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Snyder, John F, undated; Venice,FL; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Snyder, John F, undated; Guam; War Commendation; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Snyder, John F, undated; Pearl Harbor; HI; Returning Home; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sojka, Edwin S, undated; Camp Lee,VA; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sojka, Edwin S, undated; Camp Lee,VA; City Life; Poem/Old Blanford Church,Petersburg,VA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sojka, Edwin S, undated; Lakeland,FL; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sojka, Edwin S, undated; Lakeland; FL; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sojka, Edwin S, undated; APO NYC; NY; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sojka, Edwin S, undated; Daniel Field; Augusta, GA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sojka, Edwin S, undated; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sojka, Edwin S, undated; Camp Lee; VA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sojka, Alphonse, undated; Sampson NY; Completed Training; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sojka, Mitchell, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Jobs Hill Road; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sojka, Alphonse, undated; Alameda; CA; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sojko, Raymond, undated; England; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sokoleski, Mathew F, undated; Melbourne,FL; Florida Attractions; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sokoloski, Mathew F, undated; Great Lakes; IL; Finished Naval Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sokolov, Harold, undated; San Diego; CA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sokolov, Harold, undated; FPO San Francisco; CA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sonski, Alex B, undated; Big Spring; TX; Arrived for Flight Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Southwick, Lawrence, undated; Germany; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Southwick, Lawrence, undated; APO NYC; NY; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Southwick, Lawrence, undated; APO NYC; NY; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Southwick, Lawrence, undated; Champaign; IL; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sozka, Edward, undated; Greenville,SC; Railroad; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Spieker, Samuel Arnold, undated; Sasebo; Japan; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Spieker, Samuel Arnold, undated; Yokosuka; Japan; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Spieker, Samuel Arnold, undated; Mare Island; CA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Spieker, Samuel Arnold, undated; Great Lakes; IL; Completed Training as Torpedo Man's Mate; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Spiller, Herbert W, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - St Louis, Fritz, undated; Fort Bragg,NC; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - St Louis, Fritz, undated; Fort Bragg,NC; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - St Louis, Fritz, undated; Nashville,TN; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - St Louis, Wilfred, undated; Augsburg; Germany; with Description of Concentration Camp; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - St Louis, Wilfred, undated; England; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - St Louis, Wilfred, undated; Augsburg; Germany; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - St Louis, Melvin L, undated; Fort Dix; NJ; Assigned to Infantry Basic Training; Military (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stacey, Arthur, undated; Germany; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stacey, Arthur, undated; Europe; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stacey, Arthur, undated; Germany; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stacey, Arthur, undated; France; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stacey, Albert, undated; Mrs Herbert Stacey; Request for Paper; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stager, Francis W, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Son of Mrs Helen Stager; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stager, Francis W, undated; Kessler Field; Biloxi, MS; Receiving Air Force Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stager, Francis W, undated; Kessler Field; Biloxi, MS; Promotion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Staples, Leland C, undated; Leyte; Received Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stark, William C, undated; Norfolk,VA; Seabees; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stawarz, Edmund J, undated; Germany; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stawarz, Edmund J, undated; 8th Air Force; England; On List of 8th AF after VE Day; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Steele, Mason R, undated; USS Kalk; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Steele, Mason R, undated; South Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Steele, Mason R, undated; Maude Steele; Service Update,New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Steele, Mason R, undated; Maude Steele; Service Update; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stein, Arthur P, undated; Arlington; VA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stein, Edward W, undated; APO 635 New York City; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stein, Edward W, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stein, Edward W, undated; Serving Air Service Command Ord Depot; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stephenson, James, undated; South Pacific; with Enclosure; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stephenson, James, undated; APO San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stephenson, William H, undated; Where the Tradewinds Play censored Loc; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stepien, John, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Steppen, Joseph P, undated; Fort Dix; NJ; Assigned to 9th Infantry Basic Training; Military (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sternal, Anthony J, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sternal, Anthony J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Steullet, Frederich, undated; Rockville; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Steullet, Frederich, undated; Pearl Harbor; HI; In Navy When Japanese Surrendered; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stevenson, W, undated; See Stephenson, William H; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stodolski, Frank R, undated; Fort Sheridan; IL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stolarz, Henry A, undated; Norfolk,VA; Souvenir Folder; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stolarz, Henry A, undated; Duluth,MN; Souvenir Folder; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stolarz, Henry A, undated; Duluth; MN; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stolarz, Henry A, undated; Washington; DC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stoller, Jack, undated; Washington; DC; Managing Sales of War Surplus; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stowarz, Edmund J, undated; Germany; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Strycharz, Bernard M, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Strycharz, Joseph, undated; San Francisco; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Strycharz, Joseph, undated; Camp Stewart; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Strycharz, Joseph, undated; Camp Davis; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Strycharz, Joseph, undated; Hawaii; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Strycharz, Joseph, undated; Camp Pickett; VA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Strycharz, Joseph, undated; APO San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Strycharz, Joseph, undated; Hawaii; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Strycharz, Joseph, undated; South Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Strycharz, Joseph, undated; APO San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Strycharz, Joseph, undated; Blackstone Army Air Field; VA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Strycharz, Joseph, undated; Camp Stewart; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Strycharz, Joseph, undated; Camp Haan; CA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Strycharz, Joseph, undated; APO San Francisco; CA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Strycharz, Bernard M, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Belgium; Anti-aircraft; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Strycharz, Joseph, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Hawaiian Islands; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stutz, George, undated; Pacific Base; Served on USS Nevada; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Stutz, George, undated; USS Nevada; Pacific; On Nevada When Japanese Surrendered; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sullivan, George H, undated; Camp Kilmer,NJ; Humor; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sullivan, George H, undated; Charleston; SC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sullivan, George H, undated; APO NYC; NY; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sullivan, George H, undated; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sullivan, Ken, undated; Scott Field; IL; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sullivan, Ken, undated; Scott Field; IL; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sullivan, Chester, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 44 Prospect Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sulyma, William, undated; North Pacific; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sunega, Edward S, undated; 7th Army; France; Awarded Badge; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sunega, Edward S, undated; 6th Army; France; Military History, 398th Infantry; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Supina, Stephen J, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Promotion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Supina, Stephen J, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Promotion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Surdel, Edmund J, undated; Quantico; VA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Surdel, Edmund J, undated; Cherry Point; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Surdel, Edmund J, undated; Brown Field; Quantico, Va; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Surdel, Edmund J, undated; Parris Island; SC; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sutyla, Frank P, undated; Fort Bragg,NC; Camp Life; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sutyla, Frank P, undated; Algeria; Mosque; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sutyla, Frank P, undated; Grafenwhar; Germany; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Sutyla, Frank P, undated; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)